{
  "topic_id":"116",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "My best friend lives ________________ Boretz Road.",
      "choice": ["in", "on", "at", "with"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "I'll be ready to leave ________________ about twenty minutes.",
      "choice": ["by", "at", "on", "in"],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Since he met his new girlfriend, Juan never seems to be ________________ home.",
      "choice": ["on", "in", "at", "for"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "My parents have been married ________________ forty-nine years.",
      "choice": ["since", "between", "for", "until"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "My best friend, John, is named ________________ his great-grandfather.",
      "choice": ["after", "in", "to", "about"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Why are prepositions useful in writing?",
      "choice": [
        "Everyone loves a preposition!",
        "They add details to your writing.",
        "You cannot have a complete sentence without prepositions.",
        "They contain the action of the sentence."
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which pair of words is the preposition and object of the preposition in the following sentence?\nShe roasted her marshmallow over the fire.",
      "choice": [
        "She, roasted",
        "marshmallow, over",
        "over, fire",
        "the, fire"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Find the preposition.\nWill you be home for a long time?",
      "choice": ["for", "a", "will", "long"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "We sat ________________ the bench.\nWhich preposition fits in the blank?",
      "choice": ["on", "above", "below", "in"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "The bright stars sparkled ________________ me.\nWhich preposition fits best in the blank?",
      "choice": ["out", "sparkled", "on", "above"],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    }
  ]
}
